Guide to the Stanley Legum experimental linguistics collection, 1960s-1970s
George Mason University Libraries
  - Gold, Tests Auxiliary To X2 Tests In A Markov Chain (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Goodman, Simultaneous Confidence Intervals For Contrast Among Multinomial Populations (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Goodman, On Simultaneous Confidence Intervals for Multinomial Populations (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Goodman, Simple Statistical Methods For Scalogram Analysis (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Goodman, the Gospel According to Marc(ellus) Snow (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Green, A Method of Scalogram Analysis Using Summary Statistics (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Greenbaum, Contextual Influence On Acceptability Judgments (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Greenbaum, Positional Norms Adverbs (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Greenbaum, Studies In English Adverbial Usage (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Greenbaum and Quirck, Use and Attitude: The Relation Between Test Results (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Greenbaum, Frequency and Acceptability (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Griffin, Extending a Corpus: Language Games for Analyzing Pragmatics (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Grubar, Studies In Lexical Relations (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Gruber, Correlations Between the Syntactic Constructions of the Child and of the Adult (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Guttman, A Basis For Scaling Qualitative Data (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Guttman, Order Analysis of Correlation Matrices (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Huttenlocher, The Origins of Language Comprehension (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Hafner, Strong Inference and Weak Interactions (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hakes, Sentence Comprehension and Relative Pronouns (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Halle, Stress Rules In English (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hamburger, Mathematical Theory of Learning Transformational Grammar (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Harms, The ABC's of Generative Phonology, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Harms, Split Shift and Merger In the Permic Vowels (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hatch, Annual Supplement to Literature Survey On Child Language (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hatch, First Language Acquisition and Second Language Learning (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hatch, Sequencing Language Structures for Model 2 Communication Skills Program (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hatch, The Young Child's Comprehension of Relative Clauses (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hatch, The Five Year Old's Comprehension of Expanded and Transformed (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Heise, Separating Reliability and Stability In test Retest Correlation (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hempel, Deductive Nomological vs. Statistical Explanation, Scientific Explanation, Space, and Time (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hendricks, Current Trends In Discourse Analysis (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hendricks, Methodology of Narrative Structural Analysis (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Hendricks, The structural Study of Narrative: Sample Analysis (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hendricks, Style and the Structure of Literary Discourse (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hill, The Sequence of Tenses With "If" Clauses (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hiller, Review of the Literature on the Concept of Vagueness and its Defin. As a psychol. Construct (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hinds, Optional Pronominalization In Discourse (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hochster, Subordinate Clause Raising and Lexical Gap (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Holmquist, Selected Bibliography on Performative Theory (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Holzman, Ellipsis in Discourse: Implications - Computer ling. Analysis, child language acq. And semantic theory (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Hopkins, The Analysis of Repeated Measures Designs (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Howes, A Word Count of Spoken English (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hymes, The Ethnography of Speaking (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Ikegami, The Semological Structure of the English Verbs of Motion (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Jencks, What color is IQ? Intelligence and race (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Jemkins, The Comprehensive of Ambiguities (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Jenkins, On the relevance of psycho linguistic data (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Jenkins, On the relevance of psycho linguistic data (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Jenkins, Some surface linguistic classes with conceptual relevance (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Jenkins, Some surface linguistic classes with conceptual relevance (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Jenkins, Syntax Considerations in Stories for Beginning Readers (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Jensen, Discussion of (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Jensen, An embattled hypothesis (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Karni, The use of smallest space analysis in studying (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Karrer, A Chomsky Bibliography (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Karttunen, Conference and discourse (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Karttunen, Definite Description with Crossing Conference (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Karttunen, The Identity of Noun Phrases (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Karttunen, The Logic of English Predicate Complement Construction (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Karttunen, Presupposition and Ling. Context, Theoretical Linguistics (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Karttunen, Remarks on presuppositions (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Karttunen, What do Referential Indices Refer To? (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Karttunen, Syntax and Semantics of Questions (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Kasher, Mood Implicatures: A Logical Way of Doing Generative Pragmatics, Theoretical Ling (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Keats, Test Theory (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Keenan, The Logical Diversity of Natural Language (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Kimura, The Asymmetry of the Human Brain (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Kimura, Cerebral Dominance and the perception of Verbal Stimuli (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Kimura, Dual function asymmetry of the brain in visual perception (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Kimura, Left-right differences in the perception of melodies (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Kimura, Some Effect of Temporal Damage on Auditory Perception (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Kimura, Speech lateralization in young children as determined by an auditory test (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Kiparsky, FACT (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Kirsner, Natural focus and agentive interpretation: on the semantics of Dutch expletive (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Kirsner, On Pragmatic Inference and Communicative Strategies (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Kirsner, The role of Zullen in the grammar of modern standard Dutch (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Kirsner, Less is More: the Semantics of Sensory Verb Complements in English (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Klingsporn, The Significance of Variability (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Kochman, Orality and Literacy As Factors of "Black" and White communicative behavior (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Kochman, Cross-Cultural Communication: Contrasting Perspectives Conflicting Sensibilities (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Kochman, Language behavior in the negro Ghetto (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Kochman, Rapping in the black ghetto (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Kochman, The Power Axis: A Cognitive Residue of Inter-Racial Encounters (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Kochman, Social factors in the consideration of teaching standard English (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Koutsoudas, The A Over A convention (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Koutsoudas, Gapping, conjunction reduction, and coordinate deletion (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Koutsoudas, On the Non-Sufficiency of Extrinsic Order (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Krashen, On the Pseudo-cleft (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Koutsoudas, On WH-Words in English (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Koutsoudas, The Strike Order Fallacy (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Koutsoudas, Unordered Rule Hypotheses (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Koutsoudas, On the Application of Phonological Rules (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Krashen, Language and the left hemisphere, February 16, 1972 and October 1972 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Krashen, A Model of Adult Second language Performance, December 1975 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    (2 copies)
  - Krashen, Presupposition in Syntax and Semantics (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Krashen, Semantic Correlates of syntactic structure (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Krashen, The Sentence and Structure of English: A Reference Manual (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Krashen, Temporal Order (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Kurylowicz, Ergativeness and the stadial theory of linguistic develop (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Lance, Chapter 1 - Constituents of the noun phrase (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Langacker, On Pronominalization and the Chain of Command (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Langenbruch, Local Adverbials in English (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Larson, The verbal response of groups to the absence of presence of leadership (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Larson, Forms of analysis and small group problems-solving (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Leathers, Testing for determinant interactions in the small group communication process (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Legum, The Acquisition of adverbial Noun Complements (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Legum, AERA Trip Report, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Legum, Trip Report, La Jolla (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Legum, Report on Speech delivered to the 5th regional meeting (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Legum, Sketch of English adverbs (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Legum, On the node Label "adv" (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Legum, Analysis of child language survey data (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Legum, The verb particle const. In English basic or derived (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Legum, On the Acquisition of Subjoined Clauses (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Legum, Some Child language and Socio-linguistic constraints on linguistic Method theory (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Legum, Comments on Politzer an Bartley "Standard English and Nonstandard dialects" (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Legum, An Overview of linguistic Domains for Individualized Diagnostic (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Legum, Coordinate Structure in Japanese (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Legum, Comments on Politzer an Bartley "Standard English and Nonstandard dialects" (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Legum, Preliminary views on black English characteristics (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Legum, On rule ordering (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Legum, Texas conference on the goals of linguistic theory (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Legum, Social dialects and reading (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Legum, Address label program: instructions to users (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Legum, Papers, University 113 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Legum, Interaction of theoretical analyses with development of instruct. Systems (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Legum, Conceptual framework for the design of a composition program (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Legum, A basic study of English homographs - A problem in highspeed (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Legum, The Acquisition of Adverbial Noun Complements (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Legum, Art Analysis program: The offering of Cain and Abel (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Legum, Social Dialects and Their Implications for Beg. Rdg. Instruction (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Lehrer, Verbs, and deletable objects (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Levin, Leoard Type IV Errors and Interactions (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Lingoes, A Set-theoretic model for analyzing dichotomous items (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Linguistic Society of American Program
  - McCawley, How to find Semantic University in the Event that there Are Any (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - McCawley, English as a VSO language (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - McCawley, Meaning and the description of Language (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - McCawley, Where do noun phrases come from? (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Macaully, Specifically speaking., May 7, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Paper hand-out
  - Mackay, Phoneme repetition in the structure of language (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Macaulay, Agency, stativity and the character of the English verb (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Macaulay, Negative Prestige, Linguistic Insecurity and Linguistic Self-Hatred (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Macaullary, "I don't really Believe in That Middle Class you know, Myself, to be honest" (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Marascuilo, Appropriate Post Joc Comparisons for Interaction and (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Martinet, Function, structure, and sound change (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Mavrogenes, Concise Guide/Standard/Secondary and College read test (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Menzel, Complementation and Historical Syntax (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Meredith, Statistics and Data Analysis, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    Annual Review
  - Michell, The interpretation of ambiguously implicative verbs (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Milholland, Theory and Techniques of Assessment (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Milner, Comparative et relatives (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Milner, Les exclamative et le complementizer (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Montague, Pragmatics and intentional logic (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Moore, Evaluation of Five discrimination Procedures for Binary Variables (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Moore, Nonparametric Statistical methods (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Moore, Connected discourse - a methodological note (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Murray, New Statistical Techniques For Evaluating Longitudinal Models (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Oetinger, Mathematical linguistics and automatic translation (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Olney, An Analysis of English Discourse Structure (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Palermo, Language acquisition from age 5 onward (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Papcun, Is the left Hemisphere Specialized for speech, Language or Something Else (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Papers in linguistics in Honor of Leon Dostert (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Partee, Reference, conference and opacity (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Peper, Development of a scaling technique for sociometric data (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Peters, Recursiveness of language Generated by grammars (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Peters, Pseudo-Cleft Sentences (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Peters, On the generative power of transformational grammars (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Peters, English Rules (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Labeaune and Sullivan, Classroom Tryout of the SWRL Second Year Communication Skills, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Labov, [CU] Negative attraction and negative concord in various English dialects (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Labov, (UP) Negative attraction and negative concord in English grammar., March 31, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Labov, Publications reporting research on non-standard Negro English (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Labov and Labov, Learning the Syntax of Questions (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Labov, The study of Non-Standard English, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Labov, Academic Ignorance and Black Intelligence (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Labov, Memorandum: To All Georgetown Partic, December 17, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Labov, A.S.R., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Labov, The Linguistic Variable as a Structural Unit, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Labov, The Logic of Non-Standard English (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Labov, Some Sources of reading Problems for Negro Speakers of Non-Standard English, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Labov, The Reading of the Edsuffix (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Labov, Handout diagram (Box 9, Folder 14)
    (notes by S.E. Legum)
  - Labov, Contraction, Deletion, and inherent Variability of the English Copula, May 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Labov, The Social Motivation of Sound Change (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Labov, Stages in the Acquisition of Standard English (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Labov and Cohen, Some Suggestions for teaching standard Eng. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Labov and Robins, A note on the relation of reading failure (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Labov and Linde, Charlotte Spatial Networks as a site for the Study of Language and Thought (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Labov and Waletzky, Oral version of personal experience, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lakoff, Counterparts, or the problem of reference in transformational grammar (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Lakoff, Deep and surface grammar (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Lakoff, on generative semantics (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Lakoff, Pragmatics in natural logic (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Lakoff, Some thoughts on transderivational constraints (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lakoff and Peters, Phrasal conjunction and symmetric predicates (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Lakoff and Ross, Criterion for verb phrase constituency (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Lakoff and Ross, Is deep structure necessary? (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Lakoff and Ross, Ordering of Transformational Rules (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Lakoff and George and Thompson, Introducing Cognitive Grammar (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lakoff, Politeness, pragmatics and performance (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Lakoff, Some reasons why there can't be any some-any rule (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Peter and Ritchie, On Restricting the Base Component of Transformational Grammars (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Peterson, A Case for the Declarative Performative Verbs (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Peterson, Imperatives and Purpose and Reason Adverbials as Complements of Abstract Verbs in Moore (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pfaff, Analysis and Tabulation of Linguistic Variables for the Child Language Survey (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pfaff, American Anthropological Association Annual Meeting (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pfaff, Linguistic Factors in the Realization of the Copila: Suggestion for Investigation in Black English (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pfaff, Naturalistic Observational Dialect Studies: Processing and Output Format Requirements (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Pfaff, New and Revised Variables for Black Dialect Survey and Elicitation Techniques (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Pfaff, The Process of Decreolization in Black Eng. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Abstract, Conference on Pidgin and Creole Lang.
  - Pfaff, Realization of Intervocalic R in Be (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Pfaff, Social Factors in Linguistic Change (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Pfaff, Socio-Linguistic Variation - Summary of Labov Chapter III (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Pfaff, Some General Data Processing Requirements of Black Dialect and Spanish Speakers Sociolin (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Pfaff, Tense and Aspect in English (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Pfaff, Development of a Dialect Differentiation Measure for Black English: a Study of Black (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Pfaff, Spelling-to Sound Correspondences in Black English (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pope, Questions and Answers in English (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Unpublished doctoral Dissertation
  - Porch, Comparative Code Chart (Interim Version) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Postovsky, The Priority of Aural Comprehension in the Language Acquisition Process (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Project Literacy (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Quesenberry, Large Sample Simultaneous Confidence Intervals for Multinomial Proportions (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Reed, A Statistical Approach to Quantitative Linguistic Analysis (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Reed and Spicer, U of Minn. Correlation Methods of Comparative Idiolects in a Transition (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Reiersol, Linear and Non-Linear Multiple Comparisons in Logit Analysis (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Riles, Selection of schools for Elementary and Secondary Education Act Programs (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Ringen, On Evaluating Data Concerning Linguistic Intuition (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Ringen, Explanation, teleology, and Operant Behaviorism: A Study/Experimental Analysis of Purposive Behavior (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Ringen, Linguistic Institution and Introspective "Observation" (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Ringen, A Study of the Empirical Scientific Status of Transformational Generative Grammars (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Ringen, Transformational Generative Grammars as Descriptions of Idiolects (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Roeper, Rhomas and McNeill, Review of Child Language (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Rosenbaum, Identical Verb Deletion and Language Universals (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Rosenbaum, Prerequisites for Developing a Theory of Children's Comprehension of Language, February 28, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Rosenbaum, Semantics Pragmatics and Semantic Primes: Toward an Understanding of Meaning (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Rosenbaum, Semantics and Pragmatics in Language Communication (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Rosenbaum, Sentence Comprehension and Experimental Psycholinguistics: An Evaluation (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Rosenbaum, Some General Principals involved in the Child's Language Comprehension (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Rosenbaum, Zapotec Gapping as Counterevidence to Some Universal Proposals (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Rosenbaum and Kim, Some Limits on Processing, December 1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    SWRL
  - Rosenbaum, The Grammar of English Predicate Complement Construction (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ross, Alphabet Soups and Name Calling (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Ross, Auxiliaries As Main Verbs (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Ross, Adjectives As Noun Phrases (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Ross, Cyclic Nature of English Pronominalization (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Ross, Embedded Force Rules (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Ross, Gapping and The Order of Constituents (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Ross, Primacy (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Ross, The Coefficient of Concordance: A Mathematical Tool For Comparing Literary Texts (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Ross, On the Syntax of Written Black English (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Rossmiller, Stmt. Subcommittee of Education and Labor U.S. House of Representatives (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Russell, Intelligibility and Embedded Sentences (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Russell, Early English Acquisition by Young Spanish Speakers (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Russell and Snow, Acquisition of the English Auxiliary by Spanish Speaking Children (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Russell and Snow, Production of the Can/Can't Distinct (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Ruwet, Adverbs. A Note on the Question: Where do they come from? (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Sadock, Aspects of Linguistic Pragmatics (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Sankoff, dialectology (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Sasanuma, et. Al., Impairment of the Kanji and Kana Processings in Aphasic Patients (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Schanks, Conceptual Dependency: A theory of Natural Lang. Understand, Computer Sci. Dept. and Comm. On Ling. (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Scank, 'Semantics' in Conceptual Analysis, Lingua 30, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Scheffe, A method For Judging All Contrast In the Analysis of Variance (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Schegloff, Sequencing in Conversational Openings (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Schiefelbusch and Lloyd, Contents, Language Perspectives-Acquisitions, Retardation and Intervention (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Schotta, Toward Standard English Through Writing - An Experiment in Prince Edward County, Virginia (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Schrauzer and Rhead, Ascorbic Acid Abuse: Effects of Long Term Ingestion of Excess Amounts on Blood Levels (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Scott, Attitude Measurement (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Scriven, Evaluation Perspectives and Procedures in Popham (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Scriven, Explanations, Predictions, and Laws, Scientific Explanation Space and Time, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    University of Minnesota
  - Searle, Classification of Illocutionary Acts (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Shamis, et. Al., Artificial Intelligence: Bibliog. Compiled/ Schizaphenologists Perspective (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Sheldon, The Acquisition of Relative Clauses In English: the Role of the Anti-Interruption Principle (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Sheldon, On Strategies for Processing Relative Clauses: A Comparison of Children and Adults (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Sheldon, Recognition/Relative Clauses in French and English: Implication for Lang. Learning Universals (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Sheldon, The Role of Parallel Function in the Acquisition of Relative Clauses in English (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Sherman, Non-Metric Multidimensional Scaling: A Monte Carlo Study (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Shoemaker, A Fortran IV Program for the ANOVA by the Method of unweighted means (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Shuy, A Selective Bibliography on Social Dialects (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Shuy, Psycholinguistic Attitude Study: Detroit Michigan (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Shuy, A Selective Bibliography on Social Dialects (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Sixth Annual Child Language Research Forum (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Sledd, Bi-dialectalism: The Linguistic of White Supremacy (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Slobin, Early Grammatical Development in Several Language with Special Attention to Soviet Research (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Smith and Duncan, Advanced Sampling Problems, Sampling Statistics and Applications: Fund./Theory States, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Smith, Alfred Binet's Remarkable Question: Analysis of Cultural Biases (Box 10, Folder 84)